A Guide to the Student Council General Records
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Student Council General Records
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/2/4.092
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These papers were an archival transfer from the Student Council, Newcomb Hall, University of Virginia, to Special Collections, on July 31, 2009.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the general records of the University of Virginia Student Council, ca. 410 items (2 Hollinger boxes, ca. 1 linear foot), 2000–2007, including agenda and minutes of meetings, allocation letters, appropriations committee allocations, budget, by-laws, constitution, correspondence, handbooks, and a proposal "A Student Activities Support and Advising Model."
Arrangement:
These files are arranged alphabetically by the name of the file. Items formerly in notebooks have been removed and placed in folders.
Contents List
- 2006 January-2006 April Agenda and Minutes (Box-folder 1:1)
- 2005 October-2005 November Agenda and Minutes (Box-folder 1:2)
- 2005 April-2005 September Agenda and Minutes (Box-folder 1:3)
- 2004 April Agenda and Minutes (Box-folder 1:4)
- 2004 February-2004 March Agenda and Minutes (Box-folder 1:5)
- 2003 November-2004 January Agenda and Minutes (Box-folder 1:6)
- 2003 April-2003 October Agenda and Minutes (Box-folder 1:7)
- 2007 Allocation Letters (Box-folder 1:8)
- 2007 Allocation Letters (Box-folder 1:9)
- 2004 March 29 Appropriations Committee Allocations (Box-folder 1:10)
- 2004 March 29 Appropriations Committee Allocations (Box-folder 2:1)
- 2001 November 27, 2004 March 29 Appropriations Committee Allocations (Box-folder 2:2)
- 2002 April 24 Budget (Box-folder 2:3)
- 2004 November 9-2007 August 7 Bylaws, Constitution, and Passed Bills (Box-folder 2:4)
- 2005 March 14 Bylaws, Constitution, and Passed Bills (Box-folder 2:5)
- 2000 January 25-2002 April 18 Correspondence (Box-folder 2:6)
- 2001 August 10-2001 August 26 Fall Retreat 2001 (Box-folder 2:7)
- 2003 Passed Resolutions (Box-folder 2:8)
- N.D. Proposal-"A Student Activities Support and Advising Model" (Box-folder 2:9)
- 2001–2002 Registration of Student Organizations (Box-folder 2:10)
- 2002–2003 Registration of Student Organizations (Box-folder 2:11)
- 2001 May 2-2002 April 9 Student Activities Center (Box-folder 2:12)
- 2005–2006 Student Council Handbook (Box-folder 2:13)
- 2005 Student Elections-Results (Box-folder 2:14)
  Natalie Eller
  April 6, 2010